Looking at this diamond ring,
which should have been on your
finger, I know that I promise
you that I never drink again,
but I put some liquor getting
lost in my sick thoughts girl.
I'm feeling suicidal all these
demons all around me. I'm stuck
inside the cycle. I'm gonna
marry you and be happy but now
that it's all gone. I don't
know what's the family cuz you
were my only home. Memories
fill up my mind tears. They
fill up my eyes. You were so
full of life. Why did you just
die? Please come back. I've
been trying to get out of my
own mind. I'm looking for
myself. I see no sign. I need
you to take me away cuz I don't
think I ever wanna stay you got
me feeling so alone.
I look at your grave.